

## **PROFILE**

I am a Focused, Quick-learning, Skilled And Results-Oriented Front End developer with experience building websites and web applications. I specialize in JavaScript and have experience working with React and Redux. I also have experience working with Sass, NextJs, Vuejs and VueX

## CONTACT

PHONE:

- +234 8107724784
- +234 8081576539

**EMAIL** 

chineduprecious47@gmail.com

## **ADDRESS**

NO 5 Kudeti off Adeniyi Jones Ikeja Lagos State

## REFERNCE

Name:

ljeoma Idika

PHONE:

+234 8035525343

EMAIL:

IJidika@amoil.com

# **UGWUNNA PRECIOUS CHINEDU**

# **Frontend Engineer**

#### **EDUCATION**

**Federal University of Technology** 

Nov 2016-Dec 2022

Bachelor of Engineering in Petroleum Engineering

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Adrolly, Frontend Engineer

March 2021 - December 2021

- Integrated Code Changes, test code Changes and document code changes
- Wrote, modified and debugged software for clients.
- Worked Closely with Backend developers to develop a ReactJs and Redux application for users
- Created and Deployed web Pages with HTML, javascript and CSS

## BloomX, Frontend Engineer

April 2022 - July 2022

- Developed Code to complete assigned project by Deadline.
- Utilized Reactjs and Redux web framework with Git to develop various Frontend Modules.

## Ceed Solutions, Frontend Engineer

August 2022-Current

- Created Web applications with Vuejs and VueX
- Used Redux to manage the Entire state of a React application
- Worked and consumed a lot of APIs in Reactis and VueJs application
- Worked with local MongoDB

## **SKILLS**

- HTML and CSS
- JavaScript
- Reactis
- Redux
- VueJS
- VueX
- NextJs

# LINKEDIN:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ugwunna -precious-0829b9212/

- Consuming and working with REST API SQL